<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog</link>
    <description>This is where we will post updates, funding requests and copies of pertinent documents here in addition to related news.  </description>
    <item>
      <title>Why Two Blogs?</title>
      <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/16_Why_Two_Blogs.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4f76c32-d302-4b45-9458-6622082bf343</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 16:11:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>In our attempt to be transparent, while still having all the technical skills of a history teacher, we have decided that the easiest, cleanest way to be transparent is to archive all of our old documents, discussions, meeting notes, and emails to a single Transparency blog.  Information updates will happen on a sporadic basis by Jessica Chacon.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The second one will be focused on updates and news.  It will be written roughly twice a week by Catherine Leys.  (Clearly these first two entries were written by Jessica.)</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/t_Running%20Chicken.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/16_Why_Two_Blogs.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Globaleyes to Running Chicken</title>
      <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/6/4_From_Globaleyes_to_Running_Chicken.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3554ac98-2cee-42f3-8822-1fee3ec7b8e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 4 Jun 2012 16:15:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>We are rebooting this site!  We have changed our name, are redesigning the logo, and setting up new fundraisers.  We are still the same organization - working to help support the efforts of the Children&#x2019;s Rescue Mission, health initiatives and job-training for widows in Kisumu, Kenya.  Our goal is still to be a transparent organization, so you can see how decisions are made and how money is used.  We will continue to post photo updates from Kenya.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/t_GE%20Website%202009.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/6/4_From_Globaleyes_to_Running_Chicken.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>10</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
