<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates &amp;amp; News</title>
    <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>This is where we will post updates, funding requests and copies of pertinent documents here in addition to related news.  </description>
    <generator>iWeb 2.0.4</generator>
    <item>
      <title>What $$$ Can Buy</title>
      <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/20_What_$$$_Can_Buy.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b7ad74c-6f0a-48e2-8fbc-b3681f6bc6f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 10:13:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/20_What_$$$_Can_Buy_files/482644223_b5bfad1ff1_o.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Media/482644223_b5bfad1ff1_o_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:425px; height:323px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Here is a useful list to show how far money donated to Running Chicken can go.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$5 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;a bed net (lasts five years) to prevent malaria.  Malaria is the leading cause of death for children in Kenya. Proper use of insecticide-treated bed nets is the most effective malaria prevention measure available at this time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$10 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;a book for the library at the home and resource center for vulnerable children.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$25 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;a school uniform including shoes to ensure that the inability to pay this mandatory expense does not prevent a child from going to school &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$50 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;three months of medical care for all 14 residents of the home and resource center for vulnerable children &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;$100 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;New pots, pans, plates, cups and utensils for the outreach feeding program that serves more than 600 students and children in the community &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;$200 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;8 complete school uniforms, including shoes.  While primary education is free in Kenya, school uniforms are mandatory and present a prohibitive cost to families living in poverty.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;$1000 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;Six months of meals for more than 600 students.  For students at Dago Thim Primary school – many of whom walk more than 2km to and from school - this lunch is sometimes the only reliable meal of the day.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;$15,000 can buy:&lt;br/&gt;A year of operating expenses for the home and resource center for vulnerable children.  The current 14 residents and other at-risk children in the community visit the center for basic living, medical and educational resources. Meeting our goal for tonight’s event ensures that the needs of these children are met. </description>
      <enclosure url="http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/20_What_$$$_Can_Buy_files/482644223_b5bfad1ff1_o.jpg" length="57105" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Two Blogs?</title>
      <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/16_Why_Two_Blogs.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4f76c32-d302-4b45-9458-6622082bf343</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 16:11:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/16_Why_Two_Blogs_files/Running%20Chicken.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Media/Running%20Chicken.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:425px; height:283px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;In our attempt to be transparent, while still having all the technical skills of a history teacher, we have decided that the easiest, cleanest way to be transparent is to archive all of our old documents, discussions, meeting notes, and emails to a single Transparency blog.  Information updates will happen on a sporadic basis by Jessica Chacon.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The second one will be focused on updates and news.  It will be written roughly twice a week by Catherine Leys.  (Clearly these first two entries were written by Jessica.)</description>
      <enclosure url="http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/7/16_Why_Two_Blogs_files/Running%20Chicken.jpg" length="250501" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Globaleyes to Running Chicken</title>
      <link>http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/6/4_From_Globaleyes_to_Running_Chicken.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3554ac98-2cee-42f3-8822-1fee3ec7b8e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 4 Jun 2012 16:15:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/6/4_From_Globaleyes_to_Running_Chicken_files/GE%20Website%202009.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Media/GE%20Website%202009.png&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:425px; height:272px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;We are rebooting this site!  We have changed our name, are redesigning the logo, and setting up new fundraisers.  We are still the same organization - working to help support the efforts of the Children’s Rescue Mission, health initiatives and job-training for widows in Kisumu, Kenya.  Our goal is still to be a transparent organization, so you can see how decisions are made and how money is used.  We will continue to post photo updates from Kenya.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://bylochacon.com/Running_Chicken/Blog/Entries/2012/6/4_From_Globaleyes_to_Running_Chicken_files/GE%20Website%202009.png" length="310935" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
